people take a picture up anything I saw
somebody taking a picture of a picture
leave that nice picture let me get a
picture of that picture you can take as
many as you want right we went back in
the day when cameras have film you might
never remember but Google a thing called
film made you highly selective with it
but you're taking right only memorable
stuff cuz you knew you had 24 shots the
sky could be on fire that's not
memorable enough I got one shot left
and to put in work effort you had to
drop your pitches off and wait like a
week you were dreaming about the
pictures oh I can't wait to see my
pictures are they gonna be so nice you
were calling second um excuse me my
pictures ready set me right on twos if
my pictures that man need to see how I
look and you wait a whole week to see
that you took a picture of your thumb
[Music]
[Applause]
look they gave was the negatives right
did anybody ever use a negatives
negative the most you did with a
negative just hope to the sternum egg
it's my summer right
why people look at him negative see who
they look like if he was black
[Applause]
[Laughter]
then they came out with one-hour photo
deliver that one-hour photo he was like
I can get my pictures in an hour
that's just crazy talk
[Music]
can you look man some might take your
picture like come back in an hour but
what kind of phone you guys
[Music]
you got a 1g phone
ain't no iPhone sh fun I love it man
just think I fought that invented his
[__] when you could fit in your pocket
right maybe your grandparents camera it
was huge
you're like an accordion that camera was
so dangerous it had a cape on it
[Applause]
cameras used to have like eight anybody
you stand over there let me take shelter
it was someone's job to be the flash but
he just stood away
[Music]
put his life on the line for that
picture right
who's holding stick a dynamite who have
me the last guy disposition they go
mushroom clap bump they got they
pictures like three years later
who is that Ameen a picture
and they got these buttholes out there
with the selfie stick you busy let me
get a picture of myself cuz I ain't got
no friends
cuz I'm always taking pictures of myself
with the back of my hair little I yeah
[Applause]
the grandparent never knew with the back
of their head
don't get me wrong I like pitches not
alike though I like candid shots because
at least they have artistic value but
they are dangerous to take to suppose
you take a Candace out of a woman Susie
hello click click let me see that
picture let me see that oh no you gotta
lead that [__]
I got a double chin in that pitch oh you
had a double chin in real life
hey did you know Drybar company has his
own app download right now to watch save
me shake clips and watch my whole
special